Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 3: Boxes 45-66
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 3: Boxes 45-66
- Box: 51, Folder: 13 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Item 27: Causes and Remedies for Labor Turnover, Publication (Box 51, Folder 13)
    By Employers Association of Chicago. February, 1955. Item is in English.
- Box: 51, Folder: 14 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: 1974 Directory, Publication (Box 51, Folder 14)
    By Employers Assocation of Greater Chicago. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Here's Help When You Need It The Most, Publication (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: Who What Why How?, Publication (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Item 4: Business Benefit Package, Publication (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Item 5: OSHA Developments, Publication (Box 51, Folder 14)
    By Employers Assocation of Greater Chicago. November, 1974. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: EEOC Developments, Publication (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Item 7: Management-Labor News Brevities, Publication (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Item 8: Publications, Publication (Box 51, Folder 14)
    By Employers Assocation of Greater Chicago. April, 1976. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Facts & figures At A Glance: Employee Absenteeism And Turnover, Publication (Box 51, Folder 14)
    By Employers Assocation of Greater Chicago. July, 1974. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Focus On The News: License To Abuse, Publication (Box 51, Folder 14)
    By Employers Assocation of Greater Chicago. July 16, 1974. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Critical Considerations from the EAGC, Publication (Box 51, Folder 14)
    By Employers Assocation of Greater Chicago. February, 1974. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The EAGC Library, Publication (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Item 13: What Management Expects Of The Police Department, Publication (Box 51, Folder 14)
    By Roland E. Fulton. May 25, 1962. Item is in English.
- Box: 51, Folder: 15 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Constitution And By-Laws, Publication (Box 51, Folder 15)
    By Employers Association of Detroit. Adopter March 4, 1920- revised 1943. Item is in English.
- Box: 51, Folder: 16 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Articles of Incorporation And By-Laws, Publication (Box 51, Folder 16)
    By Employers' Association of Grand Rapids. Item is in English.
- Box: 51, Folder: 17 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Constituition And By-Laws, Publication (Box 51, Folder 17)
    By Employers Association of Milwaukee. Item is in English.
- Box: 51, Folder: 18 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Employers' Association of Pittsburgh, Publication (Box 51, Folder 18)
    By Employers' Association of Pittsburgh. Item is in English.
- Box: 51, Folder: 19 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: The Tyranny of Unions, Publication (Box 51, Folder 19)
    By Leigh H. Irvine. Pamphlet no.10. Item is in English.
- Box: 51, Folder: 20 (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Meetings, Publication (Box 51, Folder 20)
    April 2, 1962. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Forum Meeting, Publication (Box 51, Folder 20)
    February 21, 1961. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Forum Meeting, Publication (Box 51, Folder 20)
    December 28, 1960. Item is in English.
- Box: 51, Folder: 21 (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: The Employers' Pioneer, Publication (Box 51, Folder 21)
    By Employers' Group of Insurance Co. v.36:no.4 (1962:Apr.). Item is in English.
- Box: 51, Folder: 22 (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Articles of Association of The Employing Printers' Association of San Francisco, Publication (Box 51, Folder 22)
    By Employing Printers' Association of San Francisco. October, 1927. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: San Francisco Printing Industry Hospital And Health Fund, Publication (Box 51, Folder 22)
    By New York Life Insurance Company. Item is in English.
- Box: 51, Folder: 23 (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Why it Pays to Improve Your Business Environment, Publication (Box 51, Folder 23)
    By Employers Labor Relations Information Committee, Inc. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Because You Know ELRIC, Publication (Box 51, Folder 23)
    By John T. Thacher. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: How to make Your Business Climate work for you, Publication (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - Item 4: Purposeful Communication with your employees and their neighbors, Publication (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - Item 5: Purposeful Communication with your employees and their neighbors, Publication (Box 51, Folder 23)
    By Employers Labor Relations Information Committee, Inc. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Effective Corporate Communication: Six Elements Provide the Key, Publication (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - Item 7: You and Labor Law: a dramtic, up-to-date, color sound-strip film that promotes understanding and discussion, Publication (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - Item 8: Sampling of Communicator Reader Opinion, Publication (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - Item 9: Bibliography of New Books and Pamphlets, Publication (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - Item 10: "As a Reader of The ELRIC Communicator, Publication (Box 51, Folder 23)
    By John T. Thacher. cover letter to another publication. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Source List of Magazines, Publication (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - Item 12: Abstract of recently published material on industrial relations, employer-employee communication and current issues of importance to industry, Publication (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - Item 13: The Issues as Labor Sees Them: An Analysis of Material Appearing in Trade Union Publications During the period of January to April, 1955, Publication (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - Item 14: Communication and the Issues of Our Times, Publication (Box 51, Folder 23)
- Box: 51, Folder: 24 (Box 51, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: 70 Years of Mutual Respect and Confidence, Publication (Box 51, Folder 24)
    By Endicott Johnson. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Endicott-Johnson Workers Tanners and Shoemakers, Publication (Box 51, Folder 24)
    By Endicott Johnson. July 21, 1919. Item is in English.
- Box: 51, Folder: 25 (Box 51, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Engineering Manpower Newsletter, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    By Engineering Manpower Commission of Engineers Join Council. no.25 (1952:Oct. 15). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Engineering Manpower Newsletter, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    By Engineering Manpower Commission of Engineers Joint Council. no.26 (1952:Dec. 1). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Engineering Manpower Newsletter, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    By Engineering Manpower Commission of Engineers Joint Council. no.27 (1952: Dec. 15). Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Engineering Manpower Newsletter, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    By Engineering Manpower Commission of Engineers Joint Council. no.28 (1953:Jan. 1). Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Engineering Manpower Newsletter, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    By M. H. Tyytten. no.29 (1953:Jan. 15). Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Engineering Manpower Newsletter, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    By Engineering Manpower Commission of Engineers Joint Council. no.30 (1953:Feb. 1). Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Engineering Manpower Newsletter, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    By Engineering Manpower Commission of Engineers Joint Council. no.31 (1953:Feb. 15). Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Engineering Manpower Newsletter, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    By Engineering Manpower Commission of Engineers Joint Council. no.32 (1953:Mar. 1). Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Engineering Manpower Newsletter, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    By Engineering Manpower Commission of Engineers Joint Council. no.33 (1953:Mar. 15). Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Engineering Manpower Newsletter, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    By Engineering Manpower Commission of Engineers Joint Council. no.34 (1953:Apr. 1). Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Engineering Manpower Newsletter, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    By Engineering Manpower Commission of Engineers Joint Council. no.35 (1953:Apr. 15). Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Engineering Manpower Newsletter, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    By Engineering Manpower Commission of Engineers Joint Council. no.36 (1953:May 1). Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Engineering Manpower Newsletter, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    By Engineering Manpower Commission of Engineers Joint Council. no.37 (1953:May 15). Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Engineering Manpower Newsletter, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    By Engineering Manpower Commission of Engineers Joint Council. no.38 (1953:June 15). Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Special Bulletin, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    By Engineering Manpower Commission of Engineers Joint Council. June 15, 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Engineering Manpower Newsletter, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    By Engineering Manpower Commission of Engineers Joint Council. no.39 (1953:July 1). Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Engineering Manpower Newsletter, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    By Engineering Manpower Commission of Engineers Joint Council. no.40 (1953:July 15). Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Engineering Manpower Newsletter, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    By Engineering Manpower Commission of Engineers Joint Council. no.41 (1953:Aug. 6). Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Engineering Manpower Newsletter, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    By Engineering Manpower Commission of Engineers Joint Council`. no.42 (1953:Aug. 15). Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Engineering Manpower Newsletter, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    By Engineering Manpower Commission of Engineers Joint Council. no.43 (1953:Sep. 8). Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Engineering Manpower Newsletter, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    By Engineering Manpower Commission of Engineers Joint Council. no.44 (1953:Sep. 18). Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Engineering Manpower Newsletter, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    By Engineering Manpower Commission of Engineers Joint Council. no.45 (1953:Oct. 5). Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Engineering Manpower Newsletter, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    By Engineering Manpower Commission of Engineers Joint Council. no.46 (1953:Oct. 26). Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Engineering Manpower Newsletter, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    By Engineering Manpower Commission of Engineers Joint Council. no.47 (1953:Nov. 5). Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Engineering Manpower Newsletter, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    By Engineering Manpower Commission of Engineers Joint Council. no.48 (1953:Nov. 25). Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Engineering Manpower Newsletter, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    By Engineering Manpower Commission of Engineers Joint Council. no.49 (1953:Dec. 10). Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Engineering Manpower Newsletter, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    By Engineering Manpower Commission of Engineers Joint Council. no.50 (1953: Dec. 31). Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Engineering and Scientific Manpower Newsletter, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    By Engineering Manpower Commission of Engineers Joint Council. January 13, 1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Special Bulletin, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    By Engineering Manpower Commission of Engineers Joint Council. January 11, 1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Engineering and Scientific Manpower Newsletter, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    By Engineering Manpower Commission of Engineers Joint Council. no.52 (1954:Jan. 29). Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Engineering and Scientific Manpower Newsletter, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    By Engineering Manpower Commission of Engineers Joint Council. February 23, 1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 32: Engineering and Scientific Manpower Newsletter, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    By Engineering Manpower Commission of Engineers Joint Council. no.54 (1954:Mar. 10). Item is in English.
  - Item 33: Engineering and Scientific Manpower Newsletter, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    By Engineering Manpower Commission of Engineers Joint Council. no.55 (1954:Mar. 24). Item is in English.
  - Item 34: Engineering and Scientific Manpower Newsletter, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    By Engineering Manpower Commission of Engineers Joint Council. no.56 (1954:Apr. 7). Item is in English.
  - Item 35: Engineering and Scientific Manpower Newsletter, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    By Engineering Manpower Commission of Engineers Joint Council. no.57 (1954:Apr. 26). Item is in English.
  - Item 36: Engineering Manpower Newsletter, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    By Engineering Manpower Commission of Engineers Joint Council. June 1, 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 37: Engineering Manpower Newsletter, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    By Engineering Manpower Commission of Engineers Joint Council. June 8, 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 38: Engineering Manpower Newsletter, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    By Engineering Manpower Commission of Engineers Joint Council. no.3 (1951:June 28). Item is in English.
  - Item 39: Engineering Manpower Newsletter, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    By Engineering Manpower Commission of Engineers Joint Council. no.6 (1951:Oct. 15). Item is in English.
  - Item 40: Engineering Manpower Newsletter, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    By Engineering Manpower Commission of Engineers Joint Council. no.5 (1951:Sep. 25). Item is in English.
  - Item 41: Engineering Manpower Newsletter, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    By Engineering Manpower Commission of Engineers Joint Council. no.4 (1951:Aug. 29). Item is in English.
  - Item 42: Engineering Manpower Newsletter, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    By Engineering Manpower Commission of Engineers Joint Council. no.7 (1951:Nov. 15). Item is in English.
  - Item 43: Engineering Manpower Newsletter, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    By Engineering Manpower Commission of Engineers Joint Council. no.10 (1951:Dec. 15). Item is in English.
  - Item 44: Engineering Manpower Newsletter, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    By Engineering Manpower Commission of Engineers Joint Council. no.9 (1951:Dec. 9). Item is in English.
  - Item 45: Engineering Manpower Newsletter, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    By Engineering Manpower Commission of Engineers Joint Council. no.8 (1951:Nov. 27). Item is in English.
  - Item 46: Engineering Manpower Newsletter, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    By Engineering Manpower Commission of Engineers Joint Council. no.13 (1952:Feb. 15). Item is in English.
  - Item 47: Engineering Manpower Newsletter, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    By Engineering Manpower Commission of Engineers Joint Council. no.12 (1952:Feb. 1). Item is in English.
  - Item 48: Engineering Manpower Newsletter, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    By Engineering Manpower Commission of Engineers Joint Council. no.11 (1952:Jan. 15). Item is in English.
  - Item 49: Engineering Manpower Newsletter, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    By Engineering Manpower Commission of Engineers Joint Council. no.14 (1952:Mar. 15). Item is in English.
  - Item 50: Engineering Manpower Newsletter, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    By Engineering Manpower Commission of Engineers Joint Council. no.15 (1952:Apr. 15). Item is in English.
  - Item 51: Engineering Manpower Newsletter, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    By Engineering Manpower Commission of Engineers Joint Council. no.16 (1952:May 1). Item is in English.
  - Item 52: Engineering Manpower Newsletter, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    By Engineering Manpower Commission of Engineers Joint Council. no.17 (1952:May 15). Item is in English.
  - Item 53: Engineering Manpower Newsletter, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    By Engineering Manpower Commission of Engineers Joint Council. no.18 (1952:June 1). Item is in English.
  - Item 54: Engineering Manpower Newsletter, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    By Engineering Manpower Commission of Engineers Joint Council. no.19 (1952:June 15). Item is in English.
  - Item 55: Engineering Manpower Newsletter, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    By Engineering Manpower Commission of Engineers Joint Council. no.20 (1952:July 15). Item is in English.
  - Item 56: Engineering Manpower Newsletter, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    By Engineering Manpower Commission of Engineers Joint Council. no.21 (1952:Aug. 1). Item is in English.
  - Item 57: Engineering Manpower Newsletter, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    By Engineering Manpower Commission of Engineers Joint Council. no.22 (1952:Aug. 15). Item is in English.
  - Item 58: Engineering Manpower Newsletter, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    By Engineering Manpower Commission of Engineers Joint Council. no.23 (1952:Sep. 1). Item is in English.
  - Item 59: Engineering Manpower Newsletter, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    By Engineering Manpower Commission of Engineers Joint Council. no.24 (1952:Oct 1). Item is in English.
- Box: 51, Folder: 26 (Box 51, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Working Together in the Farmington Valley, Publication (Box 51, Folder 26)
    By The Ensign Bickford Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: 100 Years, Publication (Box 51, Folder 26)
- Box: 51, Folder: 27 (Box 51, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Letter to Congress, Publication (Box 51, Folder 27)
    By Ray M. Peterson. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Letter to the President, Publication (Box 51, Folder 27)
    By James F. Oates, Jr. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Road Ahead High or Low?, Publication (Box 51, Folder 27)
    By Glenn McHugh. Address Given before the National Association of Real Estate Boards' Annual Convention. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Mortality Improvement And Its Effect On Pension Costs, Publication (Box 51, Folder 27)
  - Item 5: The Pension Service of the Insurance Company, Publication (Box 51, Folder 27)
    By Equitable Life Assurance Society of the U.S. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: A Place For Everything And Everything In Its Place, Publication (Box 51, Folder 27)
  - Item 7: Some Observations Looking to the Future, Publication (Box 51, Folder 27)
    By Ray D. Murphy. A Talk under the auspices of the Insurance Section At the Forty-Fourth Annual Meeting of the United States Chamber of Commerce. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Thinking Through Some Of Our Social Legislation, Publication (Box 51, Folder 27)
    By James F. Oates, Jr. Address before the Los Angeles Rotary Club. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Federal Taxation: Reduction and Reform, Publication (Box 51, Folder 27)
    By James F. Oates, Jr. Address before the New Jersey Association of Real Estate Boards. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: A Third of the day, Publication (Box 51, Folder 27)
- Box: 51, Folder: 28 (Box 51, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Executives Service Bulletin, Publication (Box 51, Folder 28)
    By Metropolitan Life Insurance Company. v.22:no.3 (1944:Mar.). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Erie Railroad-its beginnings!, Publication (Box 51, Folder 28)
    By Robert E. Woodruff. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Saftey Rules, Publication (Box 51, Folder 28)
    By Erie Railroad. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Group Hospital, Surgical and Medical Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 51, Folder 28)
    By Travelers Insurance Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Why we say, "it's the men who make the erie", Publication (Box 51, Folder 28)
  - Item 6: Rules of the Operating Department, Publication (Box 51, Folder 28)
  - Item 7: Handbook of Special Instructions and Condense Bulletins, Publication (Box 51, Folder 28)
    By Erie Railroad. Hornell Region, Delaware Division. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Re-examination Card, Publication (Box 51, Folder 28)
    By Erie Railroad. Two blank personnel forms. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Group Insurance Plan: Non-operating Railroad Employees, Publication (Box 51, Folder 28)
  - Item 10: You Medical and Life Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 51, Folder 28)
    By Erie-Lackawanna Railroad. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Employee's Supplemental Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 51, Folder 28)
  - Item 12: Rules and Instructions Governing the Use and operation of Track Cards, Publication (Box 51, Folder 28)
  - Item 13: Physical and Education Qualifications of Employes, Publication (Box 51, Folder 28)
  - Item 14: The Clierical, Office, Station and Storehore Employees Agreement, Publication (Box 51, Folder 28)
  - Item 15: Rules of the Maintenance of Way Department, Publication (Box 51, Folder 28)
  - Item 16: Your Group Hospital, Surgical Medical Plan, Publication (Box 51, Folder 28)
  - Item 17: Your group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 51, Folder 28)
  - Item 18: Employees' Supplemental Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 51, Folder 28)
  - Item 19: Agreement between Erie Railroad Company and Road Constructors, Publication (Box 51, Folder 28)
  - Item 20: Agreement between Erie Railroad Company and the Employes of the Mechanical Department, Publication (Box 51, Folder 28)
  - Item 21: Scholarships for Children of Erie Employes, Publication (Box 51, Folder 28)
  - Item 22: Group Hospital, Surgical and Medical Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 51, Folder 28)
  - Item 23: The Erie Area, Publication (Box 51, Folder 28)
    By Erie Railroad. Map. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Erie-Lackawanna Railroad Company (Organizational Chart), Publication (Box 51, Folder 28)
    By Erie-Lackawanna Railroad. June 1, 1962. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Letter to members of former Eric Railroad company, Publication (Box 51, Folder 28)
    By Erie-Lackawanna Railroad. February 15, 1961. Correspondence. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Industrial Relations Activties, Publication (Box 51, Folder 28)
  - Item 27: Personnel Forms, Publication (Box 51, Folder 28)
    By Erie Railroad. 14 blank personnel forms. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Erie Road Liable for Wages It Cut, Publication (Box 51, Folder 28)
    News clipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Letter to Mr. J. Douglas Brown, Publication (Box 51, Folder 28)
    By J. J. Bernet. July 14, 1927. Correspondence. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: facts and Factors in Supervision, Publication (Box 51, Folder 28)
    By A. B. Hoff. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Letter to Mr. J. Douglas Brown, Publication (Box 51, Folder 28)
    By C. E. Denney. May 19, 1930. Correspondence. Item is in English.
  - Item 32: Personnel Forms, Publication (Box 51, Folder 28)
    By Erie Railroad. 6 blank personnel forms. Item is in English.
- Box: 51, Folder: 29 (Box 51, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Elanco Reporter, Publication (Box 51, Folder 29)
    By Elanco Products Co. v.1:no.2 (1967:Nov.). Item is in English.
- Box: 51, Folder: 30 (Box 51, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Information for Primary and General Elections, Publication (Box 51, Folder 30)
    By Howell Appling, Jr. May 24, 1961. Item is in English.
- Box: 51, Folder: 31 (Box 51, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Plant Rules and Regulations, Publication (Box 51, Folder 31)
    By Electro Auto-Lite Company. Item is in English.
- Box: 52, Folder: 1 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Contract between ESSO Standard Oil and the Independent Industrial Workers' Association, Publication (Box 52, Folder 1)
    By ESSO Standard Oil Company; Independent Industrial Workers' Association. July 1, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Disability Benefit Plan, Publication (Box 52, Folder 1)
    By ESSO Standard Oil Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: House of many rooms.. Many opportunties, Publication (Box 52, Folder 1)
    By ESSO Research and Engineering Company. June, 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Patterns of the Past, Publication (Box 52, Folder 1)
    By ESSO Standard Oil Company. January, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Survivor Benefit Plan, Publication (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: The Way to Work Together, Publication (Box 52, Folder 1)